Einstein, Hey Einstein, where's the dot boy? Huh
doc
you made it? Yeah,
welcome to my latest experiment.
This is the big one, the one I've been waiting for all my life.
It's a DeLorean.
All your questions will be answered. Roll tape.
Never mind that. Never mind that now.
Alright, I'm ready.
Good evening,
I'm dr Emmett Brown. I'm standing in the parking lot at Twin Pines Mall.
It's saturday morning october 26th, 1985 1:18 a.m.
And this is temporal experiment number one,
come on honey. Hey boy, get in there
boy
put your seatbelt on,
That's it.
Mhm.
Whoa, whoa
okay,
please note
that Einstein's clock is in precise synchronization with my control. Watch
got it right, check
good,
have a good trip Einstein.
Watch your head,
get that thing hooked up to the
car, watch this. Yeah, okay,
got it.
Got me the car. The car.
Yeah,
my calculations are correct.
When this baby hits 88 mph,
you're gonna see some serious shit,
what's this? What's this?
Oh
I tell you,
Miles
the temporal displacement occurred exactly. 1:20 a.m. And zero seconds,
jesus christ,
jesus christ doc, You disintegrated Einstein, calm down, marty,
I didn't disintegrate anything.
The molecular structure of both Einstein and the car are completely attacked.
Where the hell are they? The appropriate question is when the hell are they?
You see Einstein has just become the world's first time traveler.
I sent him
into the future,
One minute into the future to be exact
and precisely
1 21 am and zero seconds we shall catch up with him at the time received.
Wait a minute, wait a minute doc.
Are you telling me that you built a time machine
out of a DeLorean? The way I see it.
If you're gonna build a time machine into a car, why not do it? Some style besides
the stainless steel construction made the flux dispersal
look out.
Why? What is it hot? It's cold,
cold.
I've started you little devil
Einstein's clock is exactly one minute behind mine and still ticking.
He's alright, he's fine and he's completely unaware that anything happened.
As far as he's concerned, the trip was instantaneous.
That's why his watch is exactly one minute behind mine.
He skipped over that minute to instantly arrive at this moment in time.
Come here,
I'll show you how it works.
First
you turn the time circuits on
this readout tells you where you're going. This one tells you where you are.
This one tells you where you were. You input your destination time on this keypad.
Say you want to see the sign of the declaration of independence
or witness the birth of christ.
Here's A Red Letter Date
in the History of Science November 5, 1955.
Yes of course, November 5, 1955.
What? I don't get what happened.
That was the day I invented time travel.
I remember it vividly,
I was standing on the edge of my toilet hanging a clock, the porcelain was wet.
I slipped. Hit my head on the edge of the sink and when I came to I had a revelation.
A vision.
A picture in my head.
A picture of this.
This is what makes time travel possible
Flux, capacitor,
flux capacitor has taken me almost 30 years of my
entire family fortune to realize the vision of that day.
God, has it been that long?
Things have certainly changed around here.
I remember when this was all farmland, as far as the eye could see
old man peabody
on all of this.
He had this crazy idea
about breeding pine trees.
This is uh, this is heavy duty doc. This is great.
Does it run like on regular unleaded gasoline? Unfortunately.
No, it requires something with a little more kick plutonium
plutonium. Wait a minute. Are
you telling me that? This sucker is nuclear?
Hey, hey, keep rolling, keep rolling there. No, no, no, no, no.
This sucker's electrical.
But I need a nuclear reaction to generate the 1.21 gigawatts of electricity.
I need doc. You don't just walk into a store and buy plutonium.
Did you rip that off?
Of course from a group of libyan nationalists.
They wanted me to build them a bomb.
So I took their plutonium and in turn gave them
a shiny bomb casing full of used pinball machine parts.
Come on, let's get you a radiation suit. We must prepare to reload
safe now. Everything's that line.
Don't you lose those tapes now
record.
Almost got my lawyers,
who knows if they've got cotton underwear in the future.
I'm allergic to all synthetics in
the future.
Where you going? That's right. 25 years into the future.
I've always dreamed of seeing the future, looking beyond my years,
seeing the progress of mankind.
Why not?
I'll also be able to see who wins the next 25 world series.
Doc
look me up when you get there.
Indeed, I will
roll them.