so i'm going to go through the process
of importing videos from outside of mux
and expression engine
and get them into
both mugs and express engine as new
entries and new videos so to do that
we're going to use a add-on called data
grab
it's a third party add-on you can buy
from the expression engine store
it allows csvs json wordpress and other
things to be imported as entries
and i've got a test csv file i've
created it has the columns that we're
going to match up to the custom fields
like title the status uh description and
then the important one is urls and these
are both urls from multiple uh locations
like s3 and like my private server as
well as a mux id that already exists in
mux
so let's go ahead and map those i've put
the csv file on my server already to
import i'm going to hit create new csv
and i'm going to tell it that this is a
test.csv
and everything else is the same we're
going to put this in the events channel
it's going to read that csv sees the
columns so we're good so far
now we need to map the columns to
the fields in our expression engine
channel so title should be title
uh page content is going to be
description the important one here is
the mux assets is our url column
and then actually for status let's just
let's do status is
closed we're just that way we can find
them a lot easier so i'm going to hit
save this will create that we need to
test import
save
and now we've got that now the first
thing we need to do is run it and this
will create the entries and also push
the videos to mux and we'll get web
hooks and we'll see all of this
happening so i'm going to hit go
cool now it's complete i'm gonna go to
my channels hit refresh
and we should now see these closed
entries are all the new entries so if i
go to like a big clip which was a really
big clip that's going to take a little
while to import
we're going to see that it's in the
preparing status now if i go over to the
mux console we have nine new events that
were just triggered this was the
importing of those video files as new
assets
as they import i go to some of the other
ones like one might be really quick this
one should already be done because it's
already in mux we can see that it is
we can also see like music should be
done
and
uh there it is we're just waiting on the
files to upload and if we go to that big
clip we're really just waiting for
the video to finish importing and then
it will show up there so that's how you
can import a large number of videos into
mux and expression engine at the same
time whether that those videos are
already in mux
as ids or as
urls on a another
service